Look at this. That is the actual size of
the brain of a dinosaur that was this
big. Its skull was this big, but that is
the piece inside the skull that actually
held the brain. So, after they
discovered the skull, they put it
through a scanner, which helped them
reconstruct what brain would fit inside.
Scientists could then 3D print what they
think its brain actually looked like.
The shape looks like a reptile's, and
based on the size of different parts,
scientists were able to deduce what they
think this dinosaur might have been good
at. In this case, recognizing
individuals like in a herd, which is
something modern herding animals are
also good at. If you want to know more
about dinosaurs, watch this video.